<xml>
    <brief>Get information on available logging features</brief>
    <issue-id>567</issue-id>
    <desc>
        <p>This method tells which features are available when your user
        will submit or edit a log entry.</p>

        <p>Using this method is <i>always optional</i>. You never need to
        know about differences between OKAPI installations or logging
        preconditions. If a logging feature is not avaible, OKAPI will
        accept the request and return a user-friendly explanation.
        But you may use this method to improve usability of your app,
        e.g. by disabling nonfunctional options.</p>
    </desc>
    <opt name='cache_code'>
        <p>The code of the geocache to be logged. Available features for
        <a href='%OKAPI:methodargref:services/logs/submit%'>services/logs/submit</a>
        will be returned. Either this <i>or</i> the <b>log_uuid</b> argument
        must be supplied.</p>
    </opt>
    <opt name='log_uuid'>
        <p>The UUID of the log entry to be edited. Available features for
        <a href='%OKAPI:methodargref:services/logs/edit%'>services/logs/edit</a>
        will be returned. Either this <i>or</i> the <b>cache_code</b> argument
        must be supplied.</p>
    </opt>
    <opt name='logtype'>
        <p>The type of log entry the user wants to submit; one of the
        identifiers returned as <b>submittable_logtypes</b> by an earlier
        call to this method. If given, all the <b>can_</b> fields will reflect
        the capabilities for this type of log.  See the
        <a href='%OKAPI:methodargref:services/logs/entry%'>services/logs/entry</a>
        method for more information on log types.</p>
    </opt>
    <common-format-params/>
    <returns>
        <p>A dictionary of the following structure:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><b>submittable_logtypes</b> - a list of the log types your
                user can currently submit for the geocache (or which can replace
                the type of the log to be edited). Available types depend on
                many conditions, like the cache type and state.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>can_recommend</b> - string, tells if the user can add a
                recommendation for the geocache. One of the following:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <b>true</b> - the user can add a recommendation for
                        the geocache,
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>need_more_founds</b> - the user needs to
                        find more caches to add a recommendation for the
                        geocache,
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>false</b> - the user cannot recommend the cache
                        for some other reason, e.g. the user owns or already
                        recommended the cache. A submitted recommendation
                        will be ignored.
                    </li>
                </ul>
                <p>Please note that this field NOT about confirming an
                <i>existing</i> recommendation by services/logs/edit, which
                is always possible.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>rcmd_founds_needed</b> - the number of additional caches
                the user needs to find (or events to attend) to recommend this
                cache; <b>null</b> if <b>can_recommend</b> is <b>false</b>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>can_rate</b> - boolean, <b>true</b> if the user can rate
                the geocache; <b>false</b> if a submitted rating will be ignored.
                Ratings may be disabled for some cache types or for caches
                that the user already rated or owns. Some OC installations do
                not provide ratings at all.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>can_set_needs_maintenance</b> - boolean, <b>true</b>
                if the user can set or confirm a "needs maintenance" status
                of the cache by submitting <i>needs_maintenance2=true</i>;
                <b>false</b> if this argument will be ignored. Logging
                "needs maintenance" may not be available for all cache types.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>can_reset_needs_maintenance</b> - boolean, <b>true</b>
                if the user can reset a "needs maintenance" status of the cache
                (or confirm that ist still is in good shape) by submitting
                <i>needs_maintenance2=false</i>; <b>false</b> if this argument
                will be ignored. This feature is not available yet at some OC
                installations.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>has_image_positions</b> - boolean, <b>true</b> if this
                installations supports arbitrary log image ordering (see the
                <b>position</b> argument of the logs/images services).</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>The <b>can_rate</b> and <b>can_..._maintenance</b> fields currently
        are always <b>false</b> if a log UUID is supplied. OKAPI so far does
        not implement editing those log properties.</p>
    </returns>
</xml>
