<xml>
    <brief>Edit an existing log entry</brief>
    <issue-id>556</issue-id>
    <desc>
        <p>This method allows your user to change the content of own log entries.</p>
        <p>At least one of the optional parameters with submitted
        log data must be supplied.</p>
    </desc>
    <req name='log_uuid'>
        <p>ID of the log entry to be edited. The user of your Access Token
        must be the author of the log entry.</p>
    </req>
    <opt name='logtype'>
        <p>New type of the log entry. This may be one of:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <i>Will attend</i>, <i>Attended</i> or <i>Comment</i> for Event caches;
            </li>
            <li>
                <i>Found it</i>, <i>Didn't find it</i> or <i>Comment</i> for all other
                cache types.
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>For now, only the same five log types can be changed. If the log (before
        editing) is of another type, e.g. <i>Available</i>, the response will be
        success=false and an explanatory message. More log types may be editable
        in the future, so you MUST NOT rely on a success=false response for
        certain types.</p>

        <p>If your user did recommend or rate the cache and the log type is
        changed from "Found it" to something else, the recommendation and rating
        will be withdrawn.</p>
    </opt>
    <opt name='password'>
        <p>Some caches require a password in order to submit a "Found it" or
        "Attended" log entry. It must be supplied here if the log type is
        <em>changed to</em> "Found it" or "Attended". In all other cases,
        <b>password</b> is ignored.</p>
        <p>You may check if this cache requires a password with
        <b>req_passwd</b> field of the services/caches/geocache method.</p>
    </opt>
    <opt name='comment'>
        <p>New text to store with the log entry; will replace the existing text.
        The <b>comment_format</b> must be supplied with the comment.</p>
        <p>Note: Some OCPL-based sites support only BMP (Basic Multilingual Plane) Unicode
        characters on some database fields. If you submit characters from outside of
        the BMP plane (known as "supplementary planes", they include characters such
        as smiley symbols), then keep in mind that your text might be saved garbled.</p>
    </opt>
    <opt name='comment_format'>
        <p>Indicates the format of your <b>comment</b>, either <b>html</b> or
        <b>plaintext</b>.</p>
        <p><b>Important note:</b> The subset of allowed HTML elements is left undefined
        and may change in the future. For future-compatibility, you should use only
        basic formatting tags.</p>
    </opt>
    <opt name='when'>
        <p>Same as in the <a href='%OKAPI:methodargref:services/logs/submit%'>services/logs/submit</a>
        method, but without a default value.</p>
    </opt>
    <opt name='recommend' default='unchanged'>
        <p>Confirms or changes the user's recommendation for the cache; one of the
        following:</p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>true</b> - add a recommendation for the cache, if the user
            did not already recommend it. See the
            <a href='%OKAPI:methodargref:services/logs/submit%#arg_recommend'>services/logs/submit</a>
            method for more explanation,</li>
            <li><b>false</b> - if the user recommended the cache, withdraw the
            recommendation,</li>
            <li><b>unchanged</b> - no change of recommendation.</li>
        </ul>
    </opt>
    <opt name='rating' default='unchanged' infotags="ocpl-specific">
        <p>If the user rated the cache, the option <b>false</b> will withdraw
        that rating. Otherwise, it will be ignored (which includes
        installations that do not provide geocache ratings).</p>
    </opt>
    <opt name='langpref' default='en'>
        <p>Pipe-separated list of ISO 639-1 language codes. This indicates the
        order of preference in which language will be chosen for error messages.</p>
    </opt>
    <common-format-params/>
    <returns>
        <p>A dictionary of the following structure:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><b>success</b> - true, if all supplied data was saved
                successfully, or false if none of the supplied data was saved,</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>message</b> - plain-text string, a message for the user,
                which acknowledges success or describes an error (usually you
                want to display this only when success is false).</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
    </returns>
</xml>
